Time Limit: 10000ms
Case Time Limit: 3000ms
Memory Limit: 256MB


Description

In a running system, there're many logs produced within a short period of time, we'd like to know the count of the most frequent logs.
Logs are produced by a few non-empty format strings, the number of logs is N(1=N=20000), the maximum length of each log is 256.
Here we consider a log same with another when their edit distance (see note) is = 5.
Also we have 
a) logs are all the same with each other produced by a certain format string 
b) format strings have edit distance  5 of each other.
Your program will be dealing with lots of logs, so please try to keep the time cost close to O(nl), where n is the number of logs, and l is the average log length.
Note edit distance is the minimum number of operations (insert/delete/replace a character) required to transform one string into the other, please refer to httpen.wikipedia.orgwikiEdit_distance for more details.

Input

Multiple lines of non-empty strings.

Output

The count of the most frequent logs.


Sample In

Logging started for id:1
Module ABC has completed its job
Module XYZ has completed its job
Logging started for id:10
Module ? has completed its job


Sample Out

3