Time Limit: 10000ms
Case Time Limit: 1000ms
Memory Limit: 256MB

Description

Find a pair in an integer array that swapping them would maximally decrease the inversion count of the array. If such a pair exists, return the new inversion count; otherwise returns the original inversion count.

Definition of Inversion: Let (A[0], A[1] ... A[n]) be a sequence of n numbers. If i < j and A[i] > A[j], then the pair (i, j) is called inversion of A.

Example:
Count(Inversion({3, 1, 2})) = Count({3, 1}, {3, 2}) = 2
InversionCountOfSwap({3, 1, 2})=>
{
  InversionCount({1, 3, 2}) = 1 <-- swapping 1 with 3, decreases inversion count by 1
  InversionCount({2, 1, 3}) = 1 <-- swapping 2 with 3, decreases inversion count by 1
  InversionCount({3, 2, 1}) = 3 <-- swapping 1 with 2 , increases inversion count by 1
}


Input

Input consists of multiple cases, one case per line.Each case consists of a sequence of integers separated by comma.

Output

For each case, print exactly one line with the new inversion count or the original inversion count if it cannot be reduced.


Sample In

3,1,2
1,2,3,4,5

Sample Out

1
0